Hello everyone at Tachikawa Stage Garden!
Here is an announcement from Hello! Project would like to make an announcement.
Project will hold auditions for new members! Project will hold auditions for new members!
Please watch this video first!
Hello Project New Member Audition 2024
Hello Project, now in its 27th year, is looking for new members!
Every member of Hello!
It's an audition!
The important thing is to have the courage to take the first step
We will do our best to support your first step!
This time, we will hold auditions in two categories
If you love singing, dancing, and Hello Project!
If you love Hello Project, you can audition in Hello Project category.
And for those of you who want to show off your skills and personality in addition to singing and dancing
Please apply for the BEYONES Potential Division.
Why don't you join us and make your dreams come true at Hello Project?
We look forward to hearing from you!
Hello Project New Member Audition 2024 will be held again this year!
Yes, you have until September 2nd at 10am to apply!
The audition will start from today, so if you have any questions, please feel free to contact us.
Well, who says I'm eligible to apply?
You're wrong, right?
No? No?
No? No? No? Lie?
I'm just very happy to be in front of a good hand.
Thank you very much, and I'll be waiting for your entries!
And as you can see in the video, we will be holding auditions in two categories, Hello Project and Beyond Potential.
It is not possible to apply for both,
So please apply according to what you like and what you want to do.
For more information, please check the audition homepage or the official X page.
We are looking forward to receiving your applications!
We are waiting for you!
Hello! This time we have Shigeru Akiyama from Tsubaki Factory and Yu Murata from
and Yu Murata from Tsubaki Factory.
Please bear with us until the end of this interview.
This is Yuu's first time to be an MC for Halo! Please introduce yourself first of all.
I'm Yu Murata, a new member of Tsubaki Factory, a 14-year-old junior high school student from Aichi prefecture.
My hobbies are studying make-up and performing.
First of all, please introduce yourself as it's your first time to appear as an MC on the show.
I'm good at jumping rope and playing bocce ball.
My hobbies are being on camera and makeup research.
What do you mean by being on camera?
I like the idea that a lot of people will see my photos and videos, and it makes me really happy.
It's true that whenever I point the camera at Yu-chan, she always comes in with a smile on her face like this.
She's so cute with her innocence, but Yuu-chan is kind of an athletic type from my point of view, and she's always answering my questions.
I'm sure you'll be able to find a way to get a good deal on the newest and most up-to-date information about the newest and most up-to-date products and services.
I'm looking forward to her future.
I've been having a lot of fun in the dressing room lately.
I'm having a lot of fun in the backstage. I've been able to talk to the seniors on my own and I've been able to get to know them so well so quickly.
I talk to a lot of senior members like Mr. Ritogame.
I think it's easier to talk to older students because some of them are close to me in age.
Especially at night when I'm working full days.
I guess that's why I feel like they are my friends or students.
It's so cute to see them having fun and enjoying themselves, so I hope to see them again someday.
Thank you so much!
We hope to show you some of their school activities on youtube or something.
Please take a look at this video.
Please take a look.
tai
ni
I feel like I'm being blamed for all of this.
I have to get up early. I was in a bit of a hurry.
Just two more minutes. Cloudy outside the window.
It's so, so, so high and pretty.
And yet so scary.
So tiny, so tiny, so tiny.
I wonder if I can be you. I wonder what I can do.
Good night. Good morning.
Make a wish, make a wish, make a wish
Day in my life
I want what I can't give
And the things I want to protect
I was counting and I stopped worrying
Now, hurry up and eat
I'll feel stronger than ever
What's for dinner?
Like it or not.
Today without a title
And the future that's always ahead
It's a dream, a dream, let's call it a dream
We loved the same
Just like that girl I love
It's the sound of love being born
The sound of love being born
It was so loud, I'm sure no one could hear it
I walked fast home... the plane clouds were flying...
on a star that can't be touched in any way, shape or form
I light up a little, a little, a little, a little
Sometimes I hope
But I believe
I'll keep building on it
I'm home. See you soon.
Always with love
I'll do my best to hold on to it for the rest of my life
And something that won't last forever.
If you compare them...
I can't get it out of my head.
It's the season of excitement. The season of light.
It's the time of year when life awakens
More than last year.
I wonder if it will be hotter
No big losses today
And a future of days that will last forever
It's a dream, it's like a dream, it's like a dream
It's a day like a dream
Chimes accompanying the setting sun
Over the sparkling river
Swaying, shimmering, shimmering
The shape of a cat
The uneventful days
The nothingness of it all
Hundreds of times, tens of thousands of times
It's a connected miracle.
Something you'll never have.
And the things you want to protect.
I was counting.
I stopped worrying.
I ate the fan by myself.
I'd feel so much stronger.
Night and summer.
I recommend it, I hate it
Dreams, dreams, dreams
I like you.
I'll never get it right.
I'll keep on dreaming about the future.
It's a dream, it's a dream, it's a dream-like day
Thank you for watching!
Hello Project 2024 Summer All of Us at Tachikawa Stage Garden has just finished!
So how was it Rena?
This was our first time to perform with 9 members.
I also had a chance to perform with my seniors in the shuffle corner.
I learned a lot from this first day alone.
I would like to absorb a lot of things by watching the performances of our seniors and do my best.
How was it for you, Hasumi?
I was so nervous at the Shahud that all I remember was having fun.
But it was really fun and I felt really comfortable performing with the seniors.
I felt really safe because they were standing next to me, and I felt like I couldn't lose to them.
So I want to do my best for the next concerts and the ones to come.
Yes, Hinoha, how was it?
It was not the first time for me to perform in front of the audience with 9 members.
I was very nervous because it was the first time to perform with 9 members.
But we were able to have a good time performing together, so I think it was good.
And then
I have a lot of chances to perform with my seniors in the shuffle corner.
I want to grow up more and more from now on.
I also want to steal their good points from them.
I've been wearing a white costume with a hair ornament and a yellow costume.
I've been asked to wear a yellow costume, and everyone wears a costume with a different color for each group.
I've been wearing these costumes and I've realized that I'm participating in the concert as a member of Hello Project.
I hope everyone will enjoy the concert and do their best until the end.
The voices are still going to continue, so please come and join us!
That's all for now.
I'd like to talk a little bit about each other.
I'm going to talk a little bit about each other here. I'm going to ask you some questions and you're going to answer them in a quick and easy manner.
Yuutei Murata, what kind of person do you consider a positive person?
My hobby is makeup research.
I secretly use it as a reference
Hello Project member
Doyhuka!
Since joining Tsubaki Factory
The moment that made me the happiest was
Standing on the stage of Nippon Budokan.
What do you want to do in the live performance?
Stirring up the crowd.
What is your goal as a member of Tsubaki Factory?
I will do my best to show my freshness that only I can bring out and lead Tsubaki Factory.
I'm already curious about all of them, but who should I choose?
So, first of all, what would you like to do at a live performance?
I didn't expect that. Why do you want to do it?
I think I'm a pretty vocal person, and I have a big voice.
I think I have a good voice and it's very important to get people excited, so I'd like to try it.
That's nice. It's true that Yoo-chan seems to be pretty nervous backstage and at TV taping.
You're still a little nervous, but you try your best to get the audience excited.
Just by saying one word, fans will be excited. I hope you can do that someday.
And my goal is to lead the group with the joy that only I can bring out.
I'm still in junior high school, so I can only show the joy that I can show now, right?
I'm still in junior high school, so I have a joy that can only be expressed now, and I want to show it off.
You're a junior high school student, but you're also a very solid person.
Yoo-chan is a junior high school student, but she also has a strong sense of humor.
She's also a really good dancer, so I'm really looking forward to her future.
I can imagine you taking the initiative to teach the younger students.
I can really imagine it, so I'm really looking forward to seeing you in the future, and I'm also looking forward to working with you in the dance department.
I'm looking forward to seeing you in the future, and I'm also looking forward to working with you and having more dance parts in the future.
The question for Ms. Akiyama will be asked after the VTR.
Hallo! Sta.
Reiter, I can't believe you chose the name time!
Tsubaki Factory, new single, Youth Exabyte, onsite Aug. 28
I'm Ayano Kawamura from Angulum.
I'm Ayano Kawamura of Angeleum, and I'd like to make an announcement.
As of the last day of this year's fall tour
I will be graduating from Angelem and Hello Project.
I've wanted to be an idol since I was a child.
I've lived my life challenging myself in many different ways.
After graduating from Angelem
I discovered the halo project.
And I joined Halo Project.
And then I joined Angelem.
I've had a dreamy time every day so far.
I've been able to spend every day like a dream.
When I graduate from Angelem
I'm going to end my career as an entertainer
I have only a few days left.
I'll do my best
I hope to enjoy my life as an idol
I hope to enjoy my life as an idol and have a good time with my fans and all the members.
I will do my best until the end, so please support me.
I will do my best until the end, so please support me. Sta.
Next, I would like to ask Akiyama-san a question.
I will do my best.
Akiyama-san, you will celebrate your 22nd birthday this year, what kind of 22 year old do you want to be?
A cute 22-year-old.
What are you most interested in now?
Kindness.
Akiyama-san enjoys collecting accessories. What is the item you will spend the most time with this summer?
A catsuit.
What do you always keep in mind during rehearsals?
Rehearsal clothes.
It's been just a month since Tsubaki Factory
Please describe your expectations for the new organization in the following way.
Oh Chisato, oh Chisato, oh Chisato, oh Chisato, oh Chisato
With everyone, working together
Positively, already!
I know it's a little simple, but...
What I always try to keep in mind at rehearsals is... lesson clothes? Rehearsal clothes? Yes, but I'm most confident in my rehearsal clothes.
I think I have the most rehearsal clothes in Hello!
I have so many pairs that I can't even fit into them, but I really like collecting them.
I like to have things that make me excited when I see myself in rehearsal, so I try not to wear just any clothes at every rehearsal.
Another thing I'm interested in is what you said you're most interested in, kindness.
I know it's a bit of a stretch for everyone, but I was on the train today, and I felt like I should be nice to people.
I don't know...
I don't mean to be mean, of course, but I think that the more I am kind to people, the more I will get back.
I don't know why I've been thinking like that lately, but what I'm most interested in is kindness.
During rehearsals, when I make mistakes in my dancing, Akiyama-san is always so kind to me.
He's always so kind. Thank you.
Everyone in Tsubakakakuta is really warm, so I think I'm influenced by them.
I hope I can do my best in a kinder world.
Hello! We'll continue after this.
This is Natsuyaki Kimiyabi, and we're back with another episode of "Halo! This time, we have a guest.
Hello! Please tell us the name of our guest.
I'm Miu Ishii from Tsubaki Factory.
I'm very nervous, but I'll do my best to have fun.
Please give me your best regards.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Let's do our best!
I'll do my best.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
What would you like to cook this time?
Hitsumabushi eel today
I wonder if I can eat Hitsumabushi eel
I've never had it.
I really haven't.
Then it's a bit of a challenge, isn't it?
How is your cooking?
tatashi no
I have made omelet but I haven't made many other dishes.
If I have any questions until the end of the class, I will ask the teacher.
If you have any questions until the end of the class, please ask your teacher. Please assign a number.
Let's have fun until the end. I look forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
Now, teacher, what would you like to do first?
First of all, I would like to cook rice.
It takes the longest time to cook rice.
What is the amount of water you usually use at home?
When I cook 4 cups of rice, it's a little above 4.
Use this marker.
That's right.
I want to make it a little firm for Hitsumabushi, so I increase it by 1.1 times.
So it's a little over 1 cup.
5.1 cups
Let me show you up to 20.
Okay.
It's easy with the wireless bylan.
Wireless bylan, just like that.
It's just a flip of a switch.
You said you'd never eaten anything like this before.
He was surprised.
Eels?
My dad loves eels.
But I've never had it.
I've never eaten it.
Yes, but this time...
He wants to try it. I want to try it, but I don't know what it tastes like.
I'm looking forward to it.
Niogara has a peculiar taste, but it's very addictive.
It's a little refreshing with eel.
It's a little pungent. I'll put it in water.
Next, shiso leaves? Oba.
In school, or in home economics...
I made hamburgers.
That's amazing.
In school?
Yes, it was.
That's amazing.
That's pretty advanced.
You don't seem afraid of burning or anything like that.
It's a little wet.
It's nice.
It looks good.
Perfect.
I'm going to cut it again.
Yes, sir.
Next...
Negi...
Negi... my first... I passed...
Hello! Project concert.
You saw it too, right?
You said something strange.
Your favorite angle? Yes, 90 degrees.
Do you have something like this in your mind? No, it's the first time I've done it. The first time you just did it?
Was it 90?
You didn't introduce yourself the same way every time, but you said a lot of different things.
What else did you say? What else did you introduce yourself?
He said his favorite piece of equipment at the park was driving.
Isn't that original? You find stuff like that on your own?
I think about it right after I get home.
What should I do?
Sanba is soft, smiling and cute.
But I think she's very strong inside.
I think she's hiding a lot.
I think so, too.
I think so, but I want to bring out as much as I can.
I think the viewers think so, too.
That's why you're hiding it, aren't you?
I'll pull it out a little at a time.
Now the eggs are coming out.
Mushroom eggs.
You've cooked eggs before, right? Yes, I have.
I've cooked eggs before.
Just salt, a little.
Thank you. You're her mother, aren't you?
I heard you love Halo Pro. Is that true?
Is that true? Yes, it's true. I wonder which group she likes.
I wonder which group she likes. Masaki Sato used to be a member of Morning Musume.
Masaki Sato used to be a member of Morning Musume.
We kind of go back a ways.
So you're into them.
That's right.
Masaki Sato was the reason you decided to join Shunpu.
Yes.
What attracted you to Masaki?
I thought your sound frames were cool.
I didn't even know it was there. It's just one song.
I liked your performance and your facial expressions.
That's right.
Fukazawa-san and I watched a lot of videos and studied the performance.
And we study the performance. But, you know, from where I like, there are people I admire.
It's amazing that you can think that you want to be a part of it.
Maybe I'm ready now.
Let's start baking.
Let's get some oil and put it on a piece of china paper.
Put a thin layer here.
You know, it's important to control the salt level.
Put this a little bit closer to the clock.
It's warm.
It should be about this warm.
A little bit warmer.
A little bit.
Put it in. Spread it out.
Spread it out, that's it.
If that's not enough
Do it like this.
Yes, stretch it out, stretch it out.
Like this.
Bring it to your hand.
Pinch it with chopsticks like this
And check if it's okay.
Maybe it'll work.
Can you do it?
Yes.
Say, "Yes.
Yes!
Spread it, spread it!
He's going this way.
That's right.
Isn't it nice?
Beautiful!
Yes!
Isn't it nice?
Eggs are pretty hard to cook.
But, you know, they didn't burn at all.
It's perfect.
Next, let's make the sauce.
I'd like to make the sauce.
The base of the sauce.
Did you put it in?
I put it all in.
Yes, I do.
We're going to fire it up.
Fire.
I'm gonna fire it up.
Do it
Let's try it.
Let's do it with care.
Be careful.
Oh, wow!
The alcohol is gone.
Yes, sir.
Then turn off the heat.
Three tablespoons of soy sauce.
3 tablespoons soy sauce.
1.5 tablespoons sugar.
Who can eat a meal with just this?
If there are no ingredients, I use only this sauce.
If there's a little sugar, mix it in.
It's pretty viscous, but when it cools down, it's probably stiff.
When it cools down, it becomes hard and hard like candy.
It's not too strong. I think it's good.
I'll add Japanese eel.
This is the point of Miyahi vinegar.
Rinse off the curry thoroughly.
It's the kind you buy at the supermarket. It's got those things on it.
It looks delicious! Wash it off.
Of course, you can eat it as it is, but it's a little sweet.
If you cook them like this, they get burnt easily.
What a waste! It's my first time to wash off the sauce.
I've never tasted this before, but I'll wash the sauce off.
Shocking... but it seems to be moist and fluffy.
And you've already brought up a good point.
It's all voluntary.
I'm looking forward to seeing the voluntary work. That's all for this time. Let's talk about voluntary work too.
Please do.
Wow, look how plump it is!
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
This is Halo! Stay!
We'd like you to get to know Yu Murata a little better, so we'd like to dig a little deeper!
We asked her to write down her favorite things in a sketchbook, so let's talk about them while looking at the sketchbook!
Let's open the sketchbook!
Wow! So many drawings! So many, wow!
There are a lot of cute things in there, like muscats.
So, first of all, do you play soccer?
Yes, I love it. I was on the soccer team from the 4th grade to the 6th grade.
Wow.
I haven't played it recently, but when I played it in gym class in junior high...
I had a lot of fun playing soccer in gym class in junior high school, and I really want to play again.
Wow, you can play soccer. Did you have any games?
Yes, I did.
Wow.
It's rare to find a girl who can play soccer in Hello! Project, so it's kind of rare to find a girl who can play soccer, and it's kind of cool.
Well then...
Yes, when it comes to dance, Yu-chan is the one to talk about, right?
I've studied many different genres, but I think dance is a chance to see myself dance at concerts and so on, so I really like it.
I like dancing a lot, and I've written about concerts, but dancing, singing, and my own performances are all opportunities for people to get to know me.
It's a chance for people to get to know me.
I'm doing it because I love it.
You like to do it. What genre of dance have you done?
I'm a jazz dancer.
You go to a lot of jazz dances? Dance?
Yes, I've been dancing for over five years.
You're a really good dancer. You have feminine moves.
I thought she was really good at feminine moves, but she's also really good at expressing herself, so I'm really looking forward to seeing what kind of dancing she can do.
You use your body in a really soft way, and you have a really good way of showing it off.
I'm looking forward to seeing what kind of dance she'll do.
I'm looking forward to seeing what you can do in the future and I'm really looking forward to seeing what you can do in the future.
Haloste... Okay, then.
I really love gym class, and I'm as good as anyone else.
I think I'm the type of person who can do the 9 machine as well as other people, so I can show off my special skills and it's fun, so I like it.
I'm sure you'll be able to find a way to get the most out of it.
I'm good at ball sports.
Yes, throwing the ball.
I've guessed at least 10 people at "which way ball"...
I'm not sure what it is, but I'm sure it's something I'm going to have to try.
I'm not a big fan of the male type, but I do like the male type itself.
I like that kind of sushi!
I also like sour food.
Miso too?
I like miso because I'm from Aichi
Aichi people put a lot of miso on their food.
That's why they use miso
I was wondering what it was all about with the sudden miso
Light pink
There's something called member color
I like pastel colors.
Really?
I thought you liked the darker ones.
I like the light ones too.
I thought they were gorgeous.
I think they're so pretty.
I like it.
Did you have a color in mind for the members?
You had a color in mind? Like pink.
Pink is good.
When I heard "light pink".
I was so happy.
Really?
I see. That's great. But you're not just about this.
You're always so positive, and as you said at first, you're positive?
You're always so positive. Positive, like you said at first?
Yes, she's really positive.
I want everyone to know how positive she is.
Now, Yu Murata, please leave a message for those who are watching Halo! Please leave a message for the viewers of Halo!
Yes, as a member of Tsubaki Factory, I'll do my best in singing and dancing.
I'll do my best to sing and dance as much as I can as a member of Tsubaki Factory so that many people will get to know Tsubaki Factory.
Thank you for your support!
This is Camellia and Hirono in the daytime.
At the beginning of the rehearsal, I had a hard time breathing, I was so out of breath,
But after the rehearsal, I could hold my breath for a while,
I hope I will be able to perform without making any mistakes in the performance.
I hope I will be able to take it without making any mistakes on the day.
At first, I thought, "Oh no, it's just the three of us.
There were only three of us.
I was worried about whether I could do it or not,
I was really worried about whether I could do it or not,
But today, I felt like I was going to give it my all in the performance, but I was going to give it my all and do my best.
I'm going to give it my all.
I'm going to do my best.
I'll do my best.
I'm high with everyone, so everyone is cheering me on.
On the other hand, if I make a mistake, they'll say, "Wow, you're so cute, you made a mistake.
It's okay to make mistakes,
It's okay not to be in a hurry at all. Making mistakes is one of the ways to appeal to new members.
It is really important to change your mind when you make mistakes,
Don't be like this, everyone should look at me.
It's definitely a chance for the fans to grab it.
Let's all do our best.
Yes, I'll do my best. I'll do my best.
Please do.
It's okay.
What is your charm?
My smile.
It's a smile.
It's okay.
It's good.
Okay, here we go.
Three more rounds.
Please.
Yes, please.
Yes.
Come on, this shooting in the raw or in the regime of those who find the Japanese movement even perseverating now.
Mokka ku too.
Voice Watamenia you Otamenia
I'll follow my future
It's a gift for you, both your heart and your face
Let's not lose sight of each other
ururuchitaru hana tsubaki
Everlasting and everlasting
Lush forever and ever
Thank you for your work
We are Momo Akiyama of Tsubahi Factory and
and Yu Murata of Tsubahi Factory
It's time to say goodbye!
How was your first time at Haloste?
I was nervous.
I wondered if I'd be able to answer each question
I wasn't sure if I could answer properly.
But I think I was able to do it, and I'm really glad that I started with you and Akenwa.
I'm really glad.
You're so cheerful and uplifting that it really made me smile today, and I think it was a lot of fun.
Here's an announcement!
We are going to release a new single on August 28th, our first single in 11 months.
I hope that many people will be able to see Tsubaki Factory's voice and dance performance.
In addition to the fans of Tsubaki Factory, I'd like to invite the fans of other groups to come to the concert and get to know them.
I'm going to do my best so that everyone can get to know us better.
And we will be performing at Tokyo Idol Festival 2024!
Baki Factory will be performing on Sunday, August 4th.
Last year we couldn't make it, so this year there will be 11 of us and we hope to see a lot of people there.
This year, the 11 of us will do our best to bring excitement to as many people as possible.
On August 29th, Tsubaki Factory will be holding its summer festival 2024 Burning Heat at the Kawaguchiko Stella Theater.
This will be my first time to perform at the festival, and since it will be in summer, the excitement will be different from the usual concerts.
I'm expecting it to be great! I expect it to be great. So I am really looking forward to it.
The live performance at Kawaguchi Stella Theater will be totally different from what you usually see,
We are planning to do a lot of summery things this year as well, so I hope many of you will come.
I hope many of you will come. Objects members will appear more and more in this channel. Objects members will be appearing on the channel more and more.
We upload a new video every Wednesday, so please give us a high rating, leave a comment, and subscribe to our channel.
This time, we had Mao Akiyama of Tsubaki Factory and Yu Murata of Tsubaki Factory,
and Yu Murata of Tsubaki Factory.
Bye bye!
Thank you for watching.